Guide to the School of Law Records, 1914-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- General Administrative Files, 1914-1995, undated, 11.5 linear feet (8.5 boxes)
  - Registrar, Duke Law Journal, 1963-1970 (Box 68)
  - Registrar, Duke Law Journal, 1963-1970 (Box 68)
  - Registrar, Fees, 1962-1968 (Box 68)
  - Registrar, Geographical Locations of Students, 1961-1967 (Box 68)
  - Registrar, Graduated with Distinction, 1963-1968 (Box 68)
  - Registrar, Loans, 1962-1970 (Box 68)
  - Registrar, Miscellaneous Letters, 1965-1968 (Box 68)
  - Registrar, Mortality and Withdrawals Report, 1961-1967 (Box 68)
  - Registrar, Scholarships, 1960-1970 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1932-1934 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1934-1936 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1936-1937 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1937-1938 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1938-1939 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1939-1940 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1940-1941 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1941-1942 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1942-1943 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1943-1944 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1944-1945 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1945-1946 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1946-1947 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1947-1948 (Box 68)
  - Budget, 1948-1949 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1948-1950 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1950-1952 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1951-1952 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1951-1953 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1953-1954 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1954-1955 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1955-1956 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1956-1957 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1957-1958 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1959-1960 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1960-1961 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1960-1963 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1965-1967 (Box 69)
  - Budget, 1966-1968 (Box 69)
  - Law Department Expenses Notebook, 1924-1925 (Box 69)
  - Expenses Notebook, undated (Box 69)
  - Book Purchases Notebook, 1916-1919 (Box 69)
  - General Fund Check books, 1916-1923 (3 folders) (Box 69)
  - Law Publication Fund Check books, 1916-1923 (2 of 3 folders) (Box 69)
  - Law Publication Fund Check books, 1916-1923 (folder 3 of 3) (Box 70)
  - Law Library Book Selling and Lending Book, 1914-19416 (Box 70)
  - World Rule of Law Center, Seminars, 1959-1963, undated (Box 70)
  - World Rule of Law Center, Brochures, 1959-1963, undated (Box 70)
  - World Rule of Law Center, Design for Research on International Rule of Law, 1960 (2 folders) (Box 70)
  - World Rule of Law Center, Current Thought on Peace and War, 1960 (Box 70)
  - World Rule of Law Center, Booklet Series, Numbers 2, 3, 5, 7, 9, 14, 1960-1962 (Box 70)
  - World Rule of Law Center, Booklet Series, Numbers 15, 26, 36, 43, 44, 48, 1962-1971 (Box 70)
  - Placement Bulletins, 1952-1995 (8 of 12 folders) (Box 70)
  - Placement Bulletins, 1952-1995 (folders 9-12 of 12) (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Addresses and Speeches, 1932-1938 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Advertising, 1950-1954 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, American Law Student Assocation Convention, 1953-1955 (2 folders) (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Bar Organization Section, 1931-1934, undated (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Board of Governors Minutes, 1932-1936, 1957-1959, undated (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Board of Governors, 1958-1960 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Committee Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Comparative Law Section, 1931-1933, undated (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Constitution, 1952-1953, undated (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Current Decisions, 1931-1932 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Certificates for Editorial Board, 1958-1959 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Complimentary Copy Requests, 1957-1960 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Editor in Chief Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Financial Statements, 1957-1959 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Inter-office Memoranda, 1958-1959 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Magazine Editors Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Printers Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Southern Law Review Conference, 1956-1959 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Subscribers Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, General Files, 1938, 1954-1956 (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Grievances and Professional Conduct Section, 1932-1938, undated (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Honor Code, undated (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Invitations and Replies, 1932-1935, undated (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Judicial Board, 1957, undated (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association, Judicial Code, Honor Code, Constitution, 1953-1959, undated (Box 71)
  - Duke Bar Association: Judicial Board Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Law School Affairs Section, 1932-1935, undated (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association: Legal Education Section, 1932, undated (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Minutes, 1931, undated (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Minutes, 1931-1935, undated (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Minutes, Meetings Between the Board of Governors and Duke Bar Association, 1955, undated (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Miscellaneous, 1954-1955, undated (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, National Moot Court Briefs, undated (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, National Moot Court committee, 1952-1955 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, President, 1953-1958 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association: President's Correspondence, Bomar, F., 1938-1939 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association: President's Correspondence, Bomar, H., 1935-1936 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, President's Correspondence, Finley, 1932-1934 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, President's Correspondence, Frampton, G., 1940-1941 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, President's Correspondence, McGuire, 1932-1933 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, President's Correspondence, Murchison, 1933-1935 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, President's Correspondence, Rouzer, E., 1939-1940, undated (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Professional Affairs, 1938, 1952-1955 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Programs of Meetings, 1932-1941 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Notebook, 1931-1937, 1950-1952 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Publications Section, 1931-1933, 1955 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Secretarys File, 1932-1935 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Social Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Social Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Speakers File, 1954-1955 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Subscription Lists, 1952-1955 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Treasurers Records, 1933-1935 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Treasurers Reports and File, 1957 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Delinquent Subscribers, 1957-1959 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Subscription Orders, 1957-1959 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Letters of Cancellation, 1957-1959 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Direct and Library Exchange Subscriptions, 1958-1959 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal, Mailing List Changes, 1958-1961 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal correspondence, 1935-1936 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Law Journal, Lassiter, W.C. Correspondence, 1933 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal Correspondeence, 1934-1935 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal, 1937-1938 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal, First Issue, 1937-1939 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal Closed Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal Open Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Duke Bar Journal, History of, Essay, undated (Box 72)
  - Duke Bar Association, Miscellaneous, 1941, 1960, undated (Box 72)
  - Alumni Affairs: Class of 1921, undated (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1932-1935 Reunion Booklet, circa 1982-1985 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1937 Reunion, 1972 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1938-1939 Reunion Booklet, circa 1983-1984 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1940, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1942 Reunion Booklet, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1944-1946 Reunion Booklet, undated (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1947 Reunion Booklet, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1948-1949 Reunion Booklet, circa 1983-1984 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1950 Reunion Booklet, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1952 Reunion Booklet, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1954 Reunion Booklet, 1984 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1955 Reunion Booklet, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1957 Reunion Booklet, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1959 Reunion Booklet, 1984 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1960 Reunion Booklet, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1962 Reunion Booklet, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1964 Reunion Booklet, 1984 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1967 Reunion Booklet, 1982 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1969 Reunion Booklet, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1970 Reunion Booklet, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1972 Reunion Booklet, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1974 Reunion Booklet, 1984 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1975 Reunion Booklet, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1977 Reunion Booklet, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1979 Reunion Booklet, 1984 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1980 Reunion Booklet, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1982 Profile Book, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1985 Reunion Booklet, 1990 (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Class of 1987 Reunion Booklet, 1992 (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Dedication, Albany Police Pipe and Drums, 1991-1995 (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Dedication Invitation Packets, 1995 (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Dedication Programs, 1995 (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Speakers' Biographies for Dedication, 1995 (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Dedication Speeches, 1995 (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Timeline History of School of Law, undated (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Law School Dedication Ceremony, April 8, 1995 (VHS tape). A use copy will need to be made to view this item; contact research services for more information. (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Seminar 1, The Professionalization of the College Athlete, Apil 7, 1995 (S-VHS Tape). A use copy will need to be made to view this item; contact research services for more information. (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Seminar 2, Federalism, April 7, 1995 (S-VHS Tape). A use copy will need to be made to view this item; contact research services for more information. (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Seminar 3, Lawyering in Government, April 7, 1995 (S-VHS Tape). A use copy will need to be made to view this item; contact research services for more information. (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Seminar 4, Ethic Self-Determination After the Cold War, April 7, 1995 (S-VHS Tape). A use copy will need to be made to view this item; contact research services for more information. (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Seminar 5, Problems Due to the Complexity of Financial Markets and Products, April 7, 1995 (S-VHS Tape). A use copy will need to be made to view this item; contact research services for more information. (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Seminar 6, Unfunded Federal Mandates: Environmental Legislation, April 7, 1995 (S-VHS Tape). A use copy will need to be made to view this item; contact research services for more information. (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Seminar 7, Pre-Trial Prejudice in the Information Age, April 7, 1995 (S-VHS Tape). A use copy will need to be made to view this item; contact research services for more information. (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Law School Dedication Speeches at Dinner, April 8, 1995 (Audio Cassette Tape). A use copy will need to be made to view this item; contact research services for more information. (Box 74)
  - Alumni Affairs, Alumni News Bulletin, 1954-1955 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Directory, 1960, 1967 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Directory, 1935 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Directory, 1966 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Directory, 1983 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Brochures, 1986-1987 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, 50th Year Club, undated (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Newsletter, 1950-1967 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Law Alumni Weekend, 1992 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Alumni Directory, 1982, 1990 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Atlanta Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Baltimore Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Charlotte Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Dallas Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Jacksonville Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Kansas City Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Northeastern Ohio Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Orange County, North Carolina Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Orlando Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Alumni Affairs, Washington D.C. Alumni Directory, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Office of External Relations, Dean Latty Memorabilia, 1972-1973 (Box 76)
  - Law School Vision Letters, 1929 (Box 76)
  - Law School Exams, 1932-1972 (Box 76)
  - Dedication Ceremonies of Duke University School of Law, April 27, 1963, 2 inch Quadruplex Videotape (TRT 1:08:39) (Box 76, Videotape 77)
  - Address by Senator John Cooper, Duke University Law School Dedication, April 26, 1963, 2 inch Quadruplex Videotape (TRT 47:08) (Box 76, Videotape 78)
- Disciplinary Actions, 1948-1949, undated, .5 linear feet (1 box)
  This material is restricted for 75 years from date of origin. Contact research services for more information.
  - Disciplinary Actions and Materials Related to Suspected Honor Code Violations, 1948-1949, undated (4 folders) (Box 79)
- Oversize Materials, Circa 1930-1980, 6 Linear Feet (3 Oversize Folders and 1 box)
  - Blueprints of Law School Building, circa 1930 (Opaperfolder Oversize Folder 1)
  - Architectural Plans of the Law School Building, circa 1960 (Opaperfolder Oversize Folder 2)
  - Architectural Plans of the Law Library, circa 1980 (Opaperfolder Oversize Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, 1969 (Box 80)
  - Course Materials, Possibly in Preparation for the Bar, circa 1958-1963 (Box 80)